(Raj:)Water Demon.
(Howard:)Ice Dragon.
(Leonard:)Lesser Warlord
of Ka'a.
(Sheldon:)Not so fast.
(Sheldon:)Infinite Sheldon.
(Leonard:)Infinite Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Yes, Infinite Sheldon
defeats all other cards
(Sheldon:)and does not violate the
rule against homemade cards
(Sheldon:)because I made
it at work.
(Leonard:)Do you understand why people
don't want to play with you?
(Sheldon:)No...
(Sheldon:)although it's a question I've
been pondering since preschool.
(Leonard:)Hey.
Hey, your copy of Science
magazine was in my mailbox.
- Oh, thanks.
- Mm-hmm.
(Zack:)Check it out--
all about planets this month.
(Leonard:)That's an atom.
(Zack:)Agree to disagree.
(Zack:)That's what I love
about science--